create some haters so that they uh will
promote you well you know I think it's
like when the thing is is
that the sun beams regardless the sun
beams it's just dreams light some some
people will um some people
will not like the sun and you can find
so many negative things to say about the
Sun but the sun beams it doesn't and
then it hits you rather you want it to
hit you or not and you know you're going
to create haters you're going to create
people that are jealous because the the
emotion is is that you know because you
are in existence I'm no longer in
existence and that's a flawed that's a
flawed concept to have in your head that
you feel that you're inadequate that you
have to dim your lights because someone
else is dimming theirs everyone has a
purpose so if you're not in tuned with
yourself to receive you know uh what
other people how people fit in the over
overall puzzle then you're not going to
you you're not going to get it does that
I'm am I on the alignment there Ashley
true 100% um you have to you have to
believe in yourself you know what I mean
like it's it is definitely all about um
not not caring not comparing it's just
doing what you need to do for you preach
you know know it's you you are who needs
to change your direction you need to go
after what you need to go through nobody
gives a [ __ ] pardon me about who you are
no one cares yeah no one cares it's they
look at a person who is taking the
chance and taking the lead and doing
what they want and you're you're going
to get haters 100% but who
cares so don't mean to interrupt we got
commercial break and we'll be back and
if Ashley if you can mute yourself for
the next two minutes thank
you a web design company in Calgary is
taking the concept of helping others to
a whole new level and as Robin Crawford
reports it was an Okanogan man who
inspired them to use their Tech skills
to help people with
disabilities it giv a great pleasure to
introduce to you Michael D Haynes a
motivational speaker an entrepreneur and
a businessman Michael Haynes is doing it
all and I absolutely love it it's the
best job I've ever had in the beginning
Haynes admits that he didn't know how to
get his customer service Consulting
business off the ground and then he met
Ryan Perez with bow tie creative for
every website that we sell we donate uh
free websites to entrepreneurs with dis
abilities the Calgary based company
builds websites for businesses Haynes
knew he needed a website to promote
himself and Perez knew he had the tools
to help we were always talking about
working um um in the in or doing
something for the disability or for the
for people with disabilities um but we
didn't know what we were going to do and
I thought that this was a great time to
um to do something and and so we
invented this whole initiative like
pretty much around my bow TI creative
built and maintains an entire website
for hannes free of charge
he put my ideas into
action and that made my my
job so much easier it's an initiative
that the four-person company is proud of
it's especially close to PR's heart
because he himself has dyslexia I paved
my own path and that's why this this
this project means so much to me because
I want to help other people create their
paths bow TI creative is now helping
other people with mental and physical
challenges build websites across North
America all because of Michael Haynes
he's a great guy and it's fantastic
working with him and I can't wait to see
what happens next for him if you know um
anyone that has a mental or physical
disability that wants to become an
entrepreneur or you know
needs to needs help to get started in
the right direction definitely check out
our website haes hopes with the kind of
support offered by perz and his team uh
because I mean we're giving away free
websites to entrepreneurs that want to
make a difference so okay um we got a
new microphone as you can tell um and I
want to um uh like today's brace
yourself today is going to be a really
deep hustle Zone I mean every hustle
zone is different every story is
different from every entrepreneur uh we
try to highlight the the story behind
The Glory we try to highlight the person
behind the entrepreneur um just so that
you know people understand that
entrepreneurs are not a mirage I mean
they're people that just have different
habits and if you change your habits
that you can see the success that you
that you want to achieve and today's
guest okay this is how I met um today's
guest
trip in
2000 this was a club that opened up
which was all
ages and you know my friend and I at the
time Shawn Brown shout out to Shawn
Brown uh you know we just became friends
and we went to this
club and you know I saw this girl and
she was dancing on the
stage and uh you know like she was short
that's all I remember
and uh you know and then all of a sudden
we we we became friends and mutual
friends you know I I could remember
having a crush on her when I was growing
up as well I you know uh and didn't have
the heart to tell her but you know
either way that's like Old School uh you
know childhood crushes and stuff but it
was it was crazy that you know that
we've known each other for all this time
and then just recently linked up through
Linkedin
and to see that you know that we've made
you know from where we were kids we've
made so much spiritual and you know
fundamental transitions in our lives
both being
parents uh uh she she has a daughter
with cereal paly and um she does so much
she's such a great mother you know based
off of what I know and understand of
Ashley she is a great mother and um you
know also a a person that is deep and
but her business is healing so she has
two businesses where she has a mobile uh
she's a mobile yogur yoga teacher and uh
and then she's also um provides holistic
healing um and she does a wide variety
of things so this is a very special
hustle zone so I hope that you guys
stick around because this is going to
get real deep because she hits on the
topics that I love I love this kind of
conversation because I believe um
entrepreneur uh entrepreneurialism is
such a um it's a spiritual connection
between yourself as getting to know
yourself and and and being able to push
yourself to beyond the limits so I want
to welcome you Miss Ashley pedigroom
how's it going Ash Ashley hello how are
you doing I'm good how are you I'm doing
good I'm doing good so uh how what did
you think about the uh the the
introduction that was a phenomenal
introduction I was not expecting that it
was really it was it was great very raw
unrehearsed it was
excellent um so yeah uh how are you
doing I'm good I'm a little nervous but
I'm I'm good um so much to talk about
tonight um and I think
what I really want to drive home is the
point about finding our sole purpose um
we talk about
entrepreneurship and uh when we read the
definition of Entrepreneurship it says
it's a person who organizes and operates
a business or businesses taking on
greater than normal Financial Risk in
order to do so anyone reading that would
be like well why the hell would you even
want to get into entrepreneur
leadership and how I look at it I look
at it a little bit different I look at
it as you want to build a business with
your soul yeah so I look at it as a soul
driven I look at myself as a soul driven
entrepreneur
and what I mean by that is in order to
reach that state of
Entrepreneurship it's important that you
find your Soul's purpose because if you
don't find your Soul's purpose you're
going to have um
unnecessary um hardship along the
way I know quite a few entrepreneurs who
are very successful at what they do but
they are not successful in their
everyday life they're
miserable um they sacrifice way too much
um their their health is
failing and they're just not in the
right mind frame and you have to kind of
ask yourself why is that so why are you
doing what you're doing are you doing it
for
gratification are you doing it um for
status money popularity or are you doing
it um are you doing something that's
really feeding your soul and are you
able to help others do the
same and and that's really interesting
about helping others because that seems
to be a key component to what you've
been doing I just want to ask you if you
can move to the left a little bit
awesome okay um okay we got you so um
quick question so most of my user or not
users but uh most of the audience
they're going to get mad at me if I
don't ask you this okay you know that
you've you know you're you're a
successful entrepreneur but you know
what is your story you know how did you
get to so we we got all day so we want
to know oh God who you are and where you
come from my story um I grew up when I
was younger
I well there's two parts to this story
maybe three parts to this story um so
I'll kind of talk about me as a little
girl um and how I I was I was a dreamer
I uh from a young age I would come up
with silly inventions or um things that
were just probably not realistic but in
my head they were it was my passion um I
was all about coming up with the next
biggest
thing uh I
also growing up I uh um my sisters and I
we would often go to the corner store by
our house and get
candy and our dad wouldn't always give
us the money to do so so my dad was a
heavy smoker he'd pack or smoke like two
packs a day so I decided that I was
going to start selling his cigarettes to
some of the high school kids um and I
started making money money was it the
best way to make money probably not but
it gave me the money to go and buy candy
at the candy store so I was always
coming up with inventions or ways to
make money and as I got older um I just
realized that working for someone or
working a 9
to-5 I I just wasn't happy I was never
happy where I was I felt as though I was
just doing things just to do them um and
that changed for
me drastically in
2014 um I was in the corporate world oil
and gas industry making a ton of money
um and it was Comfort because I had a a
a stable check which was good but I was
forced to take a different direction
after I had my daughter so my daughter
and I suffered a very traumatic
birth um we actually had a near-death
experience she did die um and came back
to life and I was on my way out um when
I got to the hospital it was I was
actually working up until I had her I
was at work and something and I know
what that something is now something was
telling me to go home and not to go back
to
work so me being a workaholic in my past
um was fighting that decision I said you
know I need to at least go back to work
and finish some work there's a deadline
have to meet and something was telling
me no Ashley go home lay down and um go
to the
hospital so I got home um laid down woke
up with a horrible pain in my
stomach um so I called my mom and I said
you know something's wrong with me uh I
have this horrible pain I don't know
what it is and she said go to the
hospital so I called the hospital and
the first thing they said to me was go
and lay down
and uh I couldn't I said there's no way
there's something wrong so I get to the
hospital and I get to the front desk and
I look at the lady and I said I said I'm
dying and she's like no you're not
you're fine I'm like no I'm I'm dying
and uh we got to the admitting get up to
the
the put me on the bed and Amari her
heart rate was decreasing rapidly um and
what had happened was my placenta ripped
right off my uterus and uh we went in
for a C-section and I had six blood
transfusions and I was on my way out so
it was a a lifechanging experience um it
was a traumatic
experience so um I had to really shift
things um I had to think differently I
had to think about how to take care of a
child who came into the world so
violently I had to focus on making sure
I wasn't going to go insane and I had to
do something that was going to feed my
soul so I started um coming up with
different business ideas and quite a few
of them failed until uh I would say last
year when I got into the um healing and
from there it just opened up so many
doors of opportunity like you wouldn't
believe
um it has it has done a lot of um it has
has really healed my soul um there would
have been a point me telling the story I
probably wouldn't have been able to get
through it get through it I would have
cried the whole time um but I don't
anymore because I'm alive my daughter's
alive and I have been able to um find
something that I'm not only passionate
about but that has helped so many people
that I work with and it gives me the
opportunity to still be there for my
daughter a 9-to-5 job wouldn't provide
that for me and everything just worked
out so organically and so beautifully um
I have a precious little girl who is my
world um she's absolutely beautiful she
is so capable of
achieving way more than what the doctors
have have told me they told me when she
was in the hospital for 3 months they
said that she would probably never open
her eyes they said she would probably
never eat they said she'd probably never
smile they said she'd probably never she
would just be a vegetable well she's
none of those things um Amari is and
it's interesting because Amari I had
amar's name picked up five years before
I actually had her I knew I was going to
have a little girl and everyone I told
they just like how do you even know this
and you're crazy and I said no I'm gonna
have a daughter and her name's going to
be Amari
and I uh I looked up the meaning of
Amari and it suits her because it means
strength and it also means promised by
God and she was promised by God and uh
she's strong um this part I might
cry she's strong and she makes me
strong wow
so that's my journey um I look at her
every day and she is what keeps me
going so from there I've been able to
create a business where I have the um
flexibility um the
healing also I've developed well when I
was younger I had
um I always had really strong intuition
when I was younger I had uh things
happened to me that I just never talked
about um when I was younger and it all
became very
apparent after before I had her before I
had her but even stronger after I had
aari I am not only a Healer but I am
also a psychic medium surprise surprise
um I do various things I'm able to uh
connect with people in a way where I'm
able to bring up their false belief
systems and how that works it's really
interesting because it's not
uh um it's a process so they'll come see
me and I I literally see and I'm not
just saying this I see what's holding
them back in their life I can pick up a
false belief system or a trauma that
happened maybe when they're 10 years old
20 years old bring it
up identify what it is that's holding
them back and give them the tools to
move forward so I have two month
programs that I put them through um it's
extensive healing it's rapid healing but
it also breaks down a lot of
barriers um and it's guaranteed to um
provide instant shifts and changes but I
always tell my clients don't come until
you're ready because it is a very
emotional um ride because a lot of stuff
starts to surface but a lot of lot of
stuff starts to heal at the same time
it's
beautiful um so yeah
that's my summarized Journey wow I mean
that like in itself like I know with my
son you know the the the attachment that
I feel um you know just being a father
and having that un you know that that
love for you know that un I don't know
how to like it's just that Undying Love
you know
for it's um it's you can't describe it
it's very deep it's uh very very deep
and it runs so deep and it's one of
those things where you'll do anything to
protect
them um you'll do anything for
them because they're they're what they
look at you every day and uh they're
relying on you to get your crap together
you know what I mean if you don't have
their crap together
then they're not do very well so you got
to um set that example for sure yeah and
it gives you it's just you know I think
that you know I encourage people to have
children if they can because they'll
never understand that next level of life
that next level of love that just
undying love that energy that is like
almost like a
superpower and um you know but talking
about kids you you said some things
earlier in this conversation um that I I
I want to um yeah I can't see you on the
other end is that normal yes it's normal
because I have it fed through a
different I feel like I'm not looking at
you and it feels weird
so sorry it's okay it's Show Business
show
business but um so my question to you is
when it comes to what like why were you
so fixated with wanting
money me that's interesting you know
it's interest when I was younger yeah oh
um well the reason why um was because I
knew it could get me what I wanted right
um but the thing is is that's where you
kind of have to be a little bit you have
to be cautious and this is this is what
I mean by that is anyone can make money
but if it's going to
start if if it's going to um compromise
your values values and your
morals don't do
it um and that's the whole thing behind
me selling cigarettes like that could
have turned into something a little bit
deeper um had I have
not you know got in trouble for doing it
right um that could have resulted in me
maybe selling drugs when I got older you
know what I'm trying to say so that's
not a very good example of Entre
entrepreneurship but it was easy it was
easy access and it was easy money mhm
some people don't really like you know
kids I I like you see it's so funny how
you know certain people just have that
entrepreneurial dream because like when
I was a kid I was I went to a candy
store bought candy sold it to my friends
you know um I took my VCR tapes all my
Disney tapes and I would yeah yeah put
like a little uh yard sale yeah and um
there's something that you wanted
yeah but I I can say with myself like I
can speak because my mom was you know
pretty much on minimum wage and never
had anything I would go to school and
get made fun of and you know being the
only black kid in the the classroom
always felt that money I you know I said
this in the other hustle onone like I
would dream I would hope and pray that
Michael Jackson would come pick me up so
every everybody be like yo Ryan's the
man
and so I thought money could solve those
problems right and um so did were you
ever connected with any traum traumatic
experience where you felt that you
needed money oh yeah as as an as an
escape um yeah I uh grew up in a very
dysfunctional home so um like growing up
like from let's see oh my age like when
I was yeah 10 years old my my parents
divorced
so um my parents divorced my mom was
forced to raise the three of us girls um
on her own and my dad took off and there
wasn't a lot of support there um so my
mom was a single mom from that time on
and I saw the struggle and I saw the
loss we lost a lot we grew up with what
I would say is everything up until the
point up until I was 10 years old where
we lost our home um we were on
government or social assistance we had
to go to the food bank my mom had to do
what she had to do to make ends meet um
and my father you know he had uh a
longtime addiction for you know 15 years
so we went through a lot of we had it
all at one point and then we lost it so
I always had that fear of you know not
ever wanting to be in that situation
because I know how hard it was for my
mom but it was also very traumatic on
the three of us girls um because it it
was emotionally traumatic um mentally
traumatic um and
it it made me have this it it also
caused a lot of other issues for me down
the road especially with trusting and um
relying on people it was like no I I
have to rely on myself I'm not going to
ask ask for help I can't ask for help
and I can't rely on people because
people are always going to let me down
so I had this or this um false belief
that you know no one's going to help me
I have to do everything on my own and I
carried that for so long throughout my
life and I can tell you what it was a
struggle yeah I accomplished a lot on my
own but it would have been nice to have
you know help would have had help you
know and now I accept help
um opportunities come my way and I take
them because I know I'm deserving of
having them but I know that I can't do
it on my own like there's just no way so
um yeah it was very traumatic growing up
um from having your family together and
having everything provided for you and
then losing it all when did you because
you say you have a gift and um and I
like I could say that I I have a I have
a gift and I can I can see poal like I
can see um I can read someone's energy
and I can see their potential I can just
see what what their path should be I
don't you really use that gift often I
used to use it when I was a kid and get
myself in trouble um and get and get
into people's psych and get into
people's space and I realize that you
can't just get into people's space you
can't do that yeah you can't without
their permission
and yeah so you have a gift and when did
you know when did you realize that you
know like you being a psychic medium
like when did you realize that um that
this cuz during that time growing up
like when what were some of the
experiences that you had you know as a
kid um well when I was really little um
I want to say gosh I don't even really
know but I just had a memory a
reoccurring memory throughout my entire
life and it was bothering me so much it
was this might freak people out so I'm
sorry if this breaks you guys out here
but um I
had voices coming from my closet and it
wasn't no schizophrenic stuff I'm not
schizophrenic it was actual Spirit
talking to me from my closet and I um
also have reoccurring memories of me
finding comfort in sleeping in my closet
whenever I'd get scared which is quite
strange I felt comfortable there um I
never told anybody about it um because
in my home that was a a no no like that
wasn't finding comfort and sleeping in
my closet whenever um but I also would
predict as I got older I predicted
certain things that would happen happen
I predicted my daughter I predicted how
things would kind of turn out with
certain events in my life um people
would come into my life and I knew their
purpose um I just knew how to navigate
through through life intuitively without
getting too deep into a lot of trouble
um and I think that's what saved me and
that's why I'm here right now is because
I was able to use my intuition to
navigate through life um it was almost
like I've been here before things didn't
seem as they were hard like hearing my
story you would think oh my gosh like
that that's pretty harsh but it was
almost like I just naturally knew how to
navigate through all of that stuff and I
had a ton of deja vu it's like I had
been there before and I remember um
after I had Amari I didn't see her for
three days um because she was
intubated and um I walked into the
ncu and she didn't open her she didn't
have her eyes open at
all and was in there and she's like yeah
Mari hasn't opened her eyes yet and I
saw her and I said I've seen her before
and those were the words that came out
of my mouth and I said I know you and my
mom's like Ashley stop talking crazy you
don't know her you just had her I'm like
no I'm like I I I know her and I looked
over at her and I I said her name and I
swear my mom has this on video I said
Amari and she literally opened her eyes
like so slowly and turned her head and
looked at
me it was the most I have it on video
and it was the most intense moment of my
life I was like what the heck and she
just yeah it was like heard my voice and
she turned to me and opened her eyes and
that connection at that moment I was
just
like like thank you thank you for being
here thank you for not leaving this
world I need you and you need
me um and then ever since then like I've
always had the intuition but it has
definitely um became it's become more
stronger since I've embraced it now that
I'm not hiding it anymore or feeling
like I'm a weirdo or feeling as though I
I should be locked up in a cuckoo house
or whatever um since I've embraced it
like I literally people ask me how do
you see well I see I see I hear I feel I
um literally see people's failures and
successes I try to always be positive
and say hey you know what you're you're
going to do very well because that's
what I see I'm not going to be like oh
you're going to do crappy in life it's
you're going to do well but if you don't
fix this issue sorry but you're going to
have to keep learning this and until you
actually move past it
um so I've embraced it now and since
I've embraced it the opportunities like
I said have been
unless and I just feel like my soul is
whole that sounds funny but it's true
it's like this um something was missing
there um and well Amari it's like that
alone F FS fills me up but it was my my
purpose it was something that I um I
really was yearning for and I just
didn't know exactly what that
was um and that's kind of how it all
came about was um after I had her and
really embracing it not not hiding it
anymore I just want to uh you know uh I
want to address some of the people after
I had her and really embracing it
address everybody in the room uh we have
Susan watching thank you so much uh we
had a few people that shared
uh thank you to uh Susan day for sharing
thank you to Ryan Perez for sharing like
so many different
times uh Rita house uh thank you Tracy
thank you for sharing uh this is a very
again this is a very important hustle
Zone because again we all have different
um stories but we all have same habits
um when it comes to entrepreneurialism
so thank you guys all for showing up um
we have uh Michael hold on let me just
pull up his name here CU I can't see him
blind as B Michael webner saying um
harnessing intelligence where does that
come from as a question mark so we can
answer that in a few seconds here
Richard says hi hi Richard um you know
Susan uh Susan
day uh she says hi Carly says what's up
um Stephen says I want a hustle hustle
own t-shirt well click that link get
that tea get that tea
/bo
creative. or bowti creative
no.com anyway uh
so so Michael webner asks um harnessing
intelligence where does that come
from so harnessing
intelligence like me harnessing it or
just in general just in
general oh wow harnessing intelligence
life experience really um you can read
as many books as you want to but until
you actually go through something and
experience it you're not going to get
the same effect from a book okay so
harnessing intelligence comes from life
experience um learning from it um
sharing with other people
also being open to um other people
learning from other people um we we
should always be learning and it it
should never be a um when I say we
should always be learning we should
always be open to other people's views
and opinions because that's when we
learn you know we can't always say that
you know oh yeah well I've been through
this so I know I know what's best no it
doesn't work that way it's by really
tapping into everybody and learning from
everyone's experience and taking what
you can from it and um gaining that
knowledge that's what I think is true um
intelligence now what is your definition
oh so because you read the definition of
of um of being an entrepreneur but in
your path of being entrepreneur how how
does being an entrepreneur Define you um
like I said it's a it's a soul driven um
it's Soul driven entrepreneurship I look
at entrepreneurship as and it's it's a
lot of people look at it as a negative
thing they do they when they look at an
entrepreneur a lot of them I see it on
social media all the time they identify
them as Workaholics
depressed um you know greedy selfish
money
hungry um and yeah that is true for some
but I think there's a new I I'm seeing
more and more and I'm being introduced
to more and more entreneurship
their soul okay um they're creating from
their soul and they're not depressed
they're not greedy they're not
Workaholics I think workaholic is the
the worst thing to call yourself it's
actually not a compliment at all
workaholic when you think of a holic a
holic is is an addict so if you're
addicted to work you got to under you
got to real you have to look at why
you're addicted to work you know what
I'm trying to say so um at the end of
the day uh I really think that uh
entrepr it should be it should be um
creating something from your soul first
entreprene entrepreneurship second MH
it's not entrepreneurship first it's
creating from your soul first
entrepreneurship
second now um and
you just as an entrepreneur how many
people in your life um supported your um
your journey in becoming an entrepreneur
a lot um well my dad was an entrepreneur
from a very young age um he um owned and
operated well he FR he had two
franchises in the resturant my dad
wasur um and he's just he just had a
natural way of making money like he just
was a money magnet not only that but he
just had a very contagious personality
people loved him um
so he supported me from day one he gave
me a lot of Val valid information um he
went through a lot growing up you know
and I think the money at such a young
age um because he he wasn't so he wasn't
focused like he grew up in a
small one and he was a farm boy you know
and he worked hard all his life and
having that money at that age was it
doesn't happen often you know and not
only the money the responsibility that
went with it and um he suffered a lot
of a lot of hard times he became an
addict for a long time
like and he told me he's like you know
the one thing that really messed me up
was pressure he's like I couldn't handle
the pressure so he supported me and he
still supports me but he always tells me
he's like you have to be in a a right
frame of mind to get into this type of
Industry if you can't handle the
pressure this isn't for you this isn't
for you and this is where I say it's so
important to have a soul-based business
something that is is coming from your
soul because when you're doing it that
way there is no pressure that's right
when you're when you're looking at it as
a way to make money and a way to make
ends meet and a way for a way to um you
know improve your status popularity Fame
whatever it becomes pressure and that's
when I said I know a lot of
entrepreneurs who are very they're
they're famous and a lot of people know
them but they are just not mentally
sound they're
we've got issues we all have issues but
these people have issues and it's like
well you need to look at and review
things like what's going on here you
know um so yeah I have support U my dad
um I have support in the community um I
have some exciting news I'm not going to
share just yet I'm going to post it on
Facebook but I um have been presented
with another opportunity um to and it's
going to even it's going to help boost
my like her even more and you're not
going to mention it on in the hustle
Zone like come on asy like we've known
each other for all this time and you're
gonna hold out on all of you're just G
to mention it and hold out on all of our
guests my sister told me she's like
Ashley you're a maniac and she's like
you need to stop announcing things and
just do it and then then announce it I'm
like but that that's what gives me that
motivation is I if I say it out loud I'm
committed and I need to get that done if
if I don't then I procrastinate I do
like I'm not going to lie I have times
where I'm I'm the I can be the biggest
procrastinator and but it's also because
I I I push myself so hard
that uh I'll go and go and go and then I
burn out right so I'm still working on
that balance there because I it's not
I'm I'm not pushing myself because I
have to it's because I love what I
freaking do like I love my work I'm so
passionate about my work and it's not
work to me it's like it's a hobby it's
um it's fun so it's it's become a just
something I just love to do all the time
but I also need to learn how
to slow down slow it down you know well
it's like I I think everyone has that we
always have ideas in their head and I
think we just need to know how to
incubate them because yeah you know
sometimes just storing them on Evernote
I'll like store like voice notes and
stuff and come across it later I know
you know so some some of them are stale
ideas you know I have songs that I wrote
when I was a kid that I remember I mean
like it's just all about harnessing um
you know just harnessing the thought but
then putting it somewhere and storing it
really safe you know exactly I um
creative process I want to I want to
talk to you now there's a few things
that um that I want to bring up uh
there's not a lot of women on our show
so you know there's just a few questions
in terms of women and
entrepreneurialism uh and um
what's your your take on women in
entrepreneurialism because a lot of
people have this idea that you know it's
a like entrepreneurialism is a is a male
dominant um
Quest it's for everybody whether you're
female male gay black white asian
doesn't matter um entrepreneurship is
all about
passion it's about um doing what you're
passionate about doing whether you make
you know 500 bucks a month or a million
dollars a month it doesn't matter the
money doesn't matter it's open to
everybody um the whole thing with
the this is kind of a topic where okay
so women
men um women are uh very highly
intelligent beautiful creatures we are
resilient uh we know how to get through
a lot of stuff
but we also need male energy like it's
it's not just all about yeah girl power
it's working with both you know what I
mean um and I think that it's
entrepreneurship is for everyone
regardless you know it should never be a
um gender based decision on who is
better entrepreneur man or a woman or it
should just be strictly men and we've
evolved since then and I was talking to
you about this prior how I find that
this generation especially they're
getting more
support um and they kind of have more of
a mind of their own um because I was
talking to about the gay community and
like I have um someone close to me who
is who is gay and I noticed that there's
so much supports for the gay community
like I walked into
um well it's my brother I walked into
his school and there was posters
everywhere about supporting the gay
community so our minds are different now
we don't view things as a man should do
this and a woman should do this and this
is only a man's world and whatever it's
everyone's collectively coming together
to really Express themselves
individually now um in terms of the
other question I'm going to ask because
you are an attractive woman and I think
that the other thing that a lot of
people take advantage of just because
you know um that you're
attractive means that you're maybe a
pushover or that you know if you smile
at them or you you you send a text
message and all of a sudden it's um you
know it's a date and in doing business
with men you know men want to be able to
utilize that power and be like yeah you
know you know ashle she's pretty I 100%
right so tell me about your experience
being entrepreneur but also being you
know again you you know it's it's unable
pardon it's setting those boundaries
it's um you know I look at it like you
know I've come across a few um males
this past year who you know tried to
take advantage of me in that way and
it's interesting it's they'll use it in
a in a business way to get close to you
like oh it's a business business thing
and it's not so you have to use your
intuition in that sense too but people
like that as well they have lessons to
teach you about yourself right it's are
you going to let that person cross those
that line with you and if you don't
awesome what lesson did you learn and if
you do what is it that you need to
review right so as a woman in this
industry it's very crucial that the
boundaries are set and it's just
naturally A vibe that I will give off
I'm a nice person but I can be a very um
like you will know where you stand with
me type of person and that was instilled
in my head ever since I was young my mom
always told us3
girls you know make sure you you value
yourself you know um and growing up you
know going through all that it wasn't
always easy for me you know it wasn't um
you know
mistaking you know being in a
relationship thinking it was love but it
really wasn't so it's one of those
things where as you mature and you get
older and you start knowing your worth
more you you know how to set those
boundaries do do you do you believe that
your beauty is a gift or like do you VI
view it as a curse like in terms of
because I'm just to give you some
context like because I feel like some
people have innate gifts like for for
example one of my gifts I hear music all
day long and it's something that I
utilize especially to express myself or
to help others so I mean you know
someone you know uh someone like
yourself do you can you do you believe
do can you do you believe that it is a
part of you it's a gift that you can
utilize to propel or maybe
communicate outward you know because
sometimes certain messages can't be said
by everybody sometimes you need someone
to maybe you know to to be in a certain
light in order for the the message to be
carried across well um I think to be
very very honest with you and um I had a
very hard time with like I I don't look
at myself as an ugly person and I don't
look at myself as like oh I'm So
Glamorous I'm going to take a selfie
today you know I'm trying I'm not that
girl like I'm just not um and I also
suffered from um anxiety really really
bad Growing Up So if anyone looked at me
or commented at my looks or whatever I
just I shut down like I was just very um
shy so with the whole Beauty thing I
believe that that definitely comes from
inside I don't care who you are if you
are not beautiful you don't have
anything in there anything of substance
in this is all you have MH it's not
going to get you far in life period
because people see through that um there
are quite a few who don't um but the the
quality people
do
um am I Happ am I you know thankful for
my my beauty yeah I am but I'm not I
don't use it to get ahead in life in
that sense no and I and I hope that you
understand why asking this question
because 100% understand what you're I
know where you're coming from these are
things that we think about like
naturally you know oh you're head or
you're successful because you just had
it easy you know what I mean and or you
look like this or yeah 100% it's
profiling we profile people every day
you know we are constantly profiling
people if we were to if we were able to
actually sit down and have a
conversation with half the people were
profiling we'd walk away shocked
and sometimes we wouldn't sometimes we'd
be like well you're exactly what I
thought you were but a lot of the times
there's a deeper hidden meeting behind
those eyes that you see MH you know
there's a story behind that um there's a
struggle there's a pain there's a loss
there's a victory there's passion you
know but we're so caught up in you know
profiling that we don't give people the
chance or the opportunity to show that
side of themselves that's right
so we got a we have a commercial break
so we're going to come back and um we're
going to talk a little bit more about
the spiritual stuff and we're going to
we're going to delve deeper uh so if you
guys are ready to to um I want to say hi
to Steph that just came in and then
bounced out I love how I can watch
people coming in and coming out I'm
watch it all you guys you guys should be
watching these things because you know
this it's rare when you hear um you you
know it's rare when you hear really
great stories like this and we got
Germaine rickets in the house like best
producer in Calgary want to say hi
welcome to the hustle Zone my friend um
and then we had Susan da says
wow um Stephen um Wes wosi I don't know
how to pronounce your last name I
apologize but you say um you got to
dream big and
create some haters so that they uh will
promote you well you know I think it's
like when the thing is is
that the sun beams regardless the sun
beams it's just dreams light some some
people will um some people
will not like the sun and you can find
so many negative things to say about the
Sun but the sun beams it doesn't and
then it hits you whether you want it to
hit you or not and you know you're going
to create haters you're going to create
people that are jealous because the the
emotion is is that you know because you
are in existence I'm no longer in
existence and that's a flawed that's a
flawed concept to have in your head that
you feel that you're inadequate that you
have to dim your light because someone
else is dimming theirs everyone has a
purpose so if you're not in tune with
yourself to receive you know uh what
other people how people fit in the
overall puzzle then you're not going to
you you're not going to get it does that
I'm am I on the alignment there Ashley
true 100% um you have to you have to
believe in yourself you know what I mean
like it's it is definitely all about um
not not caring not comparing it's just
doing what you need to do for you preach
you know it's you you are who needs to
change CH your direction you need to go
after what you need to go through nobody
gives a [ __ ] pardon me about who you are
no one cares yeah no one cares it's they
look at a person who is taking the
chance and taking the lead and doing
what they want and you're you're going
to get haters 100% but who
cares so don't mean to interrupt but we
got commercial break and we'll be back
and if uh Ashley if you can mute
yourself uh for the next two minutes
thank
you a web design company in Calgary is
taking the concept of helping others to
a whole new level and as Robin Crawford
reports it was an Okanagan man who
inspired them to use their Tech skills
to help people with
disabilities it gives me great pleasure
to introduce to you Michael D Haynes a
motivational speaker an entrepreneur and
a businessman Michael Haynes is doing it
all and they absolutely love it it's the
best job I've ever had in the beginning
Haynes admits that he didn't know how to
get his customer service Consulting
business off the ground and then he met
Ryan Perez with bowai creative for every
website that we sell we donate uh free
websites to entrepreneurs with
disabilities the Calgary based company
builds websites for businesses he knew
he needed a website to promotee himself
and Perez knew he had the tools to help
we were always talking about working um
um in the in or doing something for the
disability for the for people with
disabilities um but we didn't know what
we were going to do and I thought that
this was a great time to um to do
something and and so we invented this
whole initiative like pretty much around
Michael bow tie creative built and
maintains an entire website for hannes
free of charge
he put my ideas into
action and that made my my
job so much e it's an initiative that
the four-person company is proud of it's
especially close to pere's heart because
he himself has dyslexia I paved my own
path and that's why this this this
project means so much to me because
because I want to help other people
create their paths bow tie creative is
now helping other people with mental and
physical challenges build websites
across North America all because of
Michael Haynes he's a great guy and it's
fantastic working with him and I can't
wait to see what happens next for him if
you know um anyone that has a mental or
physical disability that wants to become
an entrepreneur or you know needs to
needs help to get started in the right
direction definitely check out our
website Haynes hopes with the kind of
support offered by Perez and his team
more people will find the confidence to
reach their goals I have a challenge you
have a challenge there not a person
alive without a
challenge
I my challenge is more pronounced that
than yours Robin Crawford Global News
Colona
hey folks so yes um ww.bbc creative
withth a.com um you can fill out our
mailing list or you can contact me
directly and we can see about uh getting
you on the mailing list and and as as
when we sell a website we donate a free
website um also um we want to let
everyone know that if you buy a
t-shirt you're going to donate some
money towards the One Love Project or
the uh you know the disabilities program
that we have so make sure that you um
definitely um check out our our t-shirts
and the link is in the chat from Philip
Woods get that t get that get
g d a t
tee.com slbo creative and you can find
your shirts we're going to have um we're
going to have all kinds of things
hoodies you name it check it out um and
um you know make sure you buy your uh
hustle Zone t-shirt today and then we
also have the hustle Zone magazine
that's coming up so now let's bring our
guests back we got Ashley in the
house okay so and hopefully you can
unmute
yourself okay there you go and hello
hey so
now it's time let's let's go deep sea
diving we got to we're we're going to
get deep thought we already went deep
sea diing in the beginning but okay that
that was just surface level but we got
we we got something even deeper that we
can talk about now um you had mentioned
that you had something for me and um I
was nervous when you said it I'm like oh
Lord what did I
do okay
but all right so um I remember when was
it it was last year it was around this
time actually came to you with a a
failed business venture that I was going
to start I'm sorry about that it was a
good idea still a good idea but um you
were mentioning how you were going to go
see your father for the first time yeah
and uh you needed that and I'm going to
tell you why so what I'm picking out
from that
was I would say that was the missing
component um to helping you heal
um helping you find your your purpose um
if you look back to a lot of your um
business ventures genius business
ventures but you didn't
have your heart wasn't 100% into it if
that makes sense it was like you you
knew you wanted to create something for
a community but it was like something
was
missing um you were listening to your
soul so you were you knew something was
missing and it was your father it was
reuniting with or uniting with him not
reuniting uniting with him um
and seeing a part of yourself that you
haven't been able to
see and you've been able to live your
sole purpose you have created a platform
Ryan that has brought people from around
the world together there's nothing like
this um you are giving people the
opportunity to share their stories
you're giving people the opportunity to
connect with each other to create
friendships um to help build businesses
more communities you just took on uh you
created something that is just going to
impact every positive way and it's
because you found that missing
component so yeah
well I I appreciate that and I mean
right on the money cuz when I met my
father and and I encourage if you don't
know your father your mother or whatever
um if they're in good health and
mentally and you feel safe um you know
visiting them um I know I had my
apprehensions in going and first day I
get on you know I read Canada website um
going to Guyana and they're like you're
going to get AIDS and malaria and all
kinds of things before you you know when
you step on the soil and that you're
going to get robbed you know at the the
airport so you better make sure and I
had laptops and iPads and all kinds of
things there and then and
then and then guess what happens good
old social media yeah and uh I I get
down there I land and nobody shows up
and I'm the only one left at everyone
leaves I'm the only one left at the
airport okay so you can imagine my I was
like okay I'm gonna die tonight I don't
know and then I I see this man I see
this man for the first time and um such
a sweet Soul just I I seen he's just
he's the literally the the older version
of me and the way that he commands
himself and he just gave me a confidence
an air of confidence that I never knew I
had because like when people say when
they meet me they're like they're
intimidated and I I am so Meek you know
I'm really shy like I like I was telling
you earlier you know like at the
introduction like you know if I had a
crush on someone or whatever I was so
shy in telling them you know you know
how I
felt and when um when I met him I was
like okay what the [ __ ] am I doing all
this [ __ ] for okay I know I'm a I'm a
driver I know I'm a you know I you know
I I have a dominant personality so I'm
not I was so afraid of letting that go
or like letting people
see yeah I didn't want people to lose
didn't want to lose people as friends
but I don't care now hell no I just feel
more settled I feel more like there's
all these things I wanted to do I just
was afraid and I think that like just
like how you said it so yeah you're
right on the money with that one and I
haven't talked to you for over a year so
I I really uh you know I really
appreciate you sharing so um the next
let's let's talk
deep okay we're talking about
frequencies we're talking about um first
off we'll start light and then we'll
dive in the
secret a lot of
entrepreneurs have read the
book and I feel like a lot of people get
that book wrong and un they don't really
truly understand or know how to manifest
um the power of suggestion the power of
Attraction and um they just think oh I
want a house and then poof there's a
house here so what's your when it comes
to Law of Attraction and attracting good
things in your life what can you tell
our our uh
Watchers well we all have the ability to
materialize what we want so we'll have
we all have that
ability the thing is is the secret I
loved that book when it came out I read
it that that book came out like 10 years
ago or more and I read it I'm like Oh
yay now I can just get whatever I want
want um but it doesn't work that way
what they don't tell you is a portion of
what happens when what you want doesn't
actually
materialize why why did that not happen
for me well I can tell you why your soul
has other plans for you period um if we
don't get what we think we want it's
because we're we preparing ourselves and
align aligning ourselves for something
better so do you think that like I don't
mean interrupt but do you think that uh
our lives are predetermined because I
mean that would go against if it's if
our soul was everything was
predetermined then our soul would you
know then us saying that we're going to
be multi-billionaires probably for some
of us this is not going to come true and
that that that would uh you know you
could see how that would not do well for
people's confidence right exactly okay
so put it this way we have Choice called
choice we can take Road A or B C
D hiig what we have a choice to create
what we want let's say our primary focus
is I want to become a
billionaire well we both know that
that's the wrong mind set to have okay
it's good to want to like okay no let me
ask this why do you want to become a
billionaire that's what you need to ask
yourself so you have billionaire and
from those branches why do you want to
be a billionaire do you want to be a
billionaire to have status popularity
tons of chicks on the side lots of you
know I don't know parties I don't know
whatever like why do you want to be a
billionaire do you want to be a
billionaire to help people do you want
to be a billionaire to give back to
society do you want to be a billionaire
to I don't know other people start their
businesses um and then what does that
feel like to you when I say the word
billionaire Ryan what kind of what kind
of feeling do you get well I can say for
myself I I chose a billionaire because
millions are can can even buy you
charman toilet paper Okay um just with
inflation and and all that good stuff
the billionaire was because just like
some people say hey I want to be a
lawyer I want to be a doctor I want to
be a Healer I said I want to be a
billionaire and I chose that as a
challenge to myself um because this is
something that you know when I affirmed
it I didn't believe it I was like okay
I'm just going to choose something and
I'm going to affirm it and um and I'm
going to just choose that path uh I know
all with all intents and purposes that
you know whether I have a billion
dollars or a dollar in the bank I'm
still going to be rying you know um I'm
going to still have my Volkswagen Golf
I'm still going to have like certain
things in my life where I'm just going
to be steady I don't want the I don't
want it for monetary gain or power I do
want to establish a generation uh for my
future family and for my my my grandkids
and stuff I really want to build like
you know what aon's doing and building
solar power um solutions for places in
Africa you know if there's anything that
I want right now let me tell you
okay I want I want I want to be engaged
in again I want to get
married I want to have another kid or
two and then I want to have a greenhouse
I want to be able to grow my own
[ __ ] vegetables excuse
my okay that's all I see myself buying
with that billion dollars is being able
to grow my own vegetables there go
because I hate the fact that I'm eating
all this crap yeah I agree so does that
answer your question 100% but that
billion dollars has nothing to do with
what you
want that's true you get what I'm trying
to say yeah those things can come to you
without having a billion dollars that's
what's so interesting
about frequency and energy and law of
attraction is we place it it seems like
people place the value of money on all
this and that's not how it works yeah
you can definitely become a billionaire
in the next like six years that's fine
but what you just told me what you just
told me like what you want is coming
from your
soul you can easily get that without
having to create a billion
dollars um and you will
you've already started to that's that's
the thing is you've already started down
that path I believe 100% that things are
predetermined and the reason
why
see myself because of he actually uh can
you can you repeat that again uh your um
the internet connection is starting to I
don't know if the if your iPad is
plugged in there but
you're I'm dying yeah my good oh no okay
can you hear me now I can hear you now
um but it's still a little bit pixelated
so um I don't know if there's a way for
you to plug it in um I'm gonna have to
yeah plug it in and see what happens
here this is a hustle Zone this is all
raw um folks and um cuz we're going to
be editing a lot of this stuff we put up
the hustles on
magazine
magazine all right give me one second oh
it's okay take your
time again folks ww. creative.com um
you'll be able to see the hustle own
blog through bti creative um that's all
going to be integrated um I'm so happy
to have you guys in uh we have Godfree
to live battle he was he has his uh hand
on his ch
emoon so uh he's just like hm that's my
cousin that's my cousin that's my cousin
that's a good point from
Texas yeah that's my cousin from good
from Texas that's shout out to Jeff
shout out to Jeff and then we have
Michael D Thomas II this is very
interesting to me since my father was a
medium who read run stones for a very
long time and I'm interested if Ashley
reads tarot cards or maybe is it just a
part of spiritualist religion Ryan Perez
I think she may need to
refresh um yeah we're going to see what
we can do about that um
good
yeah yeah I think we're good let me just
double
check you are
great yay woo
um so tarot cards um I started off using
cards I don't anymore um I just read a
person's
energy and so going back to what you
were saying before um you know the
billion dollars because like for me it's
not about the monetary issue at all it
was just that I said you know people say
I want to be this I'm like I'm going to
be that I'm going to show you that I
can't I mean um whether I become it or
not that's you know the the Stars
universe and all that stuff have to line
the thing at the end of the you're
always going to be taken care of you're
you're going to have what you want you
just told me what you want right yeah
who says you have to be a billionaire to
have your
own you you said you wanted your own
Farm you can grow your own
Foods your own space you want children
you want married what that has to do
with what does that have to do with
being a billionaire for being a can you
settle for being a millionaire
could you settle for making $50,000 or
$50,000 a month could you settle for
that I don't
know no I'm playing I I mean I could
settle for it but I really wanted to you
know there's there's there's a story
behind it and and um I know there is
that's why I'm wanting to you to tell me
because you're not you're not saying
well because I grew up knowing that um I
grew up just disenfranchised just right
from the womb and yeah always uh being
put against the odds and you know I
wanted to to prove to people that when
you when you can tap into your internal
energy that you can
achieve anything that you put your mind
to you can you know for me my goal and
not to just have a farm but you know
anyone that knows me personally is like
I'm going to get I'm going to start
backpacking I'm going to go around the
world build institutions build
entrepreneur schools for Youth and start
to put in their mind that they can do
they can they can be someone greater if
someone just gives them the tools so
there's things like that I don't want
the personal billion for myself I just
want to be able to have enough wealth
that I can make you know some
fundamental changes not just you know
change by me voicing you know my
concerns is this is what you feel and
you know this is what you want to do you
need to start
writing need to write it
down
totally okay writing it down you write
it down you set you're already the thing
is is you're already planting those
seeds and I'll tell you something
interesting when I say this and it's
very very true we can have a plan okay
we can write down our plan we can say
this is what we want
but it doesn't always work out the way
that we plan it what happens is it
actually works out better than we
expected one we can say this is I know
this to be true because I over and over
and over again um because our vibration
will naturally gravitate to what we need
in our lives what we need to get us to
that point that we want to be at um if
we have a very low vibrational frequency
we're not going to get what we want it's
going to be a constant struggle but that
comes from false belief systems what
false what false belief systems are you
still hanging on to that you need to
release that you need to let go of you
know our false belief system was all
about feeling like The
Outsider because you felt as though a
part of your idty like you your father
shared that connection for many years
for many years without even actually
physically meeting and you were longing
for that so you felt like an outsider
okay
so so your your your frequency the
vibration that you're putting out there
was feeling as though you needed to do
everything on your
own right hustle on your own do
everything on your own and you probably
had a hard time accepting help
mhm
Pride right so you need to sit down you
need to start writing out what you want
but have no attachment to it if that
makes sense yeah that makes sense it's
having no attachment to to what it is or
how it's going to work out but you just
know it's going to work out the way it's
supposed to and it's going to
happen 100% it's going to happen this is
the problem is people don't believe that
and that's why they're stuck because
they're stuck in that mind frame state
of mind sorry state of mind that things
have to be so
hard things only happen to to certain
people you know what I mean and it's not
like
that wow not at
all so you set your goals and your
intentions and what you want instead of
just saying it you write it out you told
me what you wanted do you do you do you
actually do you have that written down
somewhere do you really firmly believe
it I I did have it written down but I I
I put it on a banner on you on Facebook
but I never really um you know I had
Ryan Perez the billionaire but I took it
down um but I I you know to be honest I
haven't written it down like physically
haven't really like you know I I haven't
wrote up PL cuz a lot of it's in my in
my head right like I you know when I
hang on thoughts like I don't really um
you know and I should get in more of the
habit of doing that but yeah you're
right I haven't I yeah um but I do want
to go back to the secret because I think
we kind of veed off so the secret like
we were talking about it shows you that
you know what you put out you receive
but it doesn't tell you the part about
breaking those false belief systems so
that you can actually start receiving
right so for example how do I how do I
say this so let's say I'm like oh yeah I
want to okay I I'll give you a prime
example it was 2008 I already I posted
posted a video of this so I'm going to
make it really short long story short I
left a a relationship I was engaged I
left a relationship because I just I
needed to be alone to figure out what's
what's going on with Ashley so this is
in 2008 and I was in a really bad space
I was drinking every night for like two
months I was pretty much turning into a
full-fledged alcoholic rapidly and I was
I wasn't eating like I was very
unhealthy um but the thing is is this is
where you start shifting things you
can't tell yourself oh yeah I want to be
super successful but live a very
unsuccessful
life okay so you're not matching your
vibration you're you're very opposite so
what I had to do was I actually had to
sit down with myself be I had to be
honest with
myself and I I told myself this is what
I want this is what I'm going to get
I want to go to Africa so bad I want to
buy a condo so bad I want a job I want
all this kind of stuff but the thing is
is I actually wanted it and I wasn't
going to allow any anything stop me from
getting there right I was allow myself
to stop from getting there so clean up
my ACT okay so
um all those things that I wanted I got
in less than a year H but it's because
I knew I deserved it I went through can
you see me okay yeah I can I can you
move on to the other uh can you move
closer to the left I think it's your
left it's my left but it's
yeah okay
perfect I had to know that I was
deserving of those things so my false
belief systems these are what I this is
what I was hanging on
to I was hanging on to the fear of
feeling stupid I was hanging on to the
fear of not succeeding I was hanging on
to the fear of constantly having to
struggle throughout my life because
that's what I was taught at a young age
that anything you want in life you have
to struggle to get it um I was taught
that um I wasn't smart enough because
when I was younger I was told I had a
disability because I couldn't grasp um
the French uh French immersion I was in
French immersion I couldn't grasp it you
know and I started having these seizures
these severe seizures in the middle of
class for like over a year and I was
just I couldn't felt like I couldn't get
my crap together so I had a lot of false
belief systems and I sat down with
myself and I said yeah I'm holding
myself back and change is going to feel
very uncomfortable but if I don't change
here quickly I'm going to be not in a
good
space so I pushed myself mentally and it
was hard like I'm not even going to tell
you how hard it was but it was really
really hard but I was able to do it MH
it's not impossible so in order for you
to really go after what you want you
really have to know that you're
deserving of it but you also have
to dig deep and hit those those dark
spots
that um need to surface that need to
come up that need go because that's
what's stalking you what about now um
you know before we're going to have to
shut this down pretty soon here
uh but one question is just briefly here
what's your your take about food and how
that makes up the um you know your your
wellness and your you know keep
you% um food it's really interesting as
I don't even know anymore and the reason
why I say that is you just made a good
point like the food that we're eating
nowadays like I go to the grocery store
why does everything look so
perfect you know what am I putting in my
body I say support local I think we need
to start supporting
local um farm-based
Foods um we need to you know it's it's
it's crucial that we're feeding
ourselves with um clean clean Foods um
for me it's because of I know you too
and it's true being an entrepreneur it's
hard to find that ballot sometimes um
and I've gained a little bit of weight
over over this past six months because
I'm happy now no but no I no it's uh
because I love my food I love pasta like
I if I could have pasta every single day
I would be happy but now you're making
me hungry for me it's um like I have to
do the whole juicing thing for me to get
in all of my my vegetables and my fruits
because I'm so busy like I'm a busy busy
person but nutrition is extremely
important
but there's also something called treat
yourself too right you have to treat
yourself once in a while but nutrition
is extremely important getting in all
that nutrients you need especially here
like in the winter we need our vitamin D
you know we're all vitamin D deficient
and we need that boost of energy but I
say stop buying food at the grocery
store Go Local if you can you know yeah
um there's
actually a website
um a friend of mine created it's a
website you can go on and you can go on
to a bunch of different um local um food
sources companies it's called um let me
just pull it up
here
um if I can find it yeah it's called Lo
local fresh source so it's
www.calfresh.ca.gov
Dory of all the mo the local um Foods
around here I'm going to pull this up
for everybody here so it is um hold on
I'm just going to just take a quick
screenshot so you guys can see what it
looks like um looks pretty cool so can
so local fresh food source and this is
pretty much a directory
to uh find the nearest local producers m
oh this is cool and then they allow you
to list on here yeah so um we need to we
need to start doing that I think us as a
a a nation really needs to we need to
rise up and start taking ownership for
our health and what we're putting in our
body you know support those local
farmers that's where you're going to get
the the high- grade quality food that
you need why the grocery
stores think about that mhm
total and food is medicine I I feel like
you know we we take we take pills like
you know with no thought in mind but we
don't think that the food that we eat
doesn't change the chemistry you know
and trying it do you know we need we
need a lot of energy and sometimes you
know certain certain foods that we're
trying to process like certain Meats
like I try to stay away from red meat
and whatnot because yeah I'm chicken and
fish yeah yeah same here digest except
for oh say that again I said I can't
digest it properly red me
yeah so
that yeah you know it's like there's
certain foods that we should and if I
could eat be and and I just you know I
had a pizza and the pizza had meatless
pepperoni and it was amazing yeah it was
I go for vegetarian pizza every time
yeah it was good and I'm kind of leaning
towards that next part of my life right
just trying to wean myself even off meat
because you know I want longevity you
know and I love the the way that you
know natural food makes me feel you know
I I I my third eye is strengthened and I
know it I know cuz we need as
entrepreneurs we need that energy
throughout the day and if I don't get
that I'm sorry I brew my own colloidal
silver
and that in itself it's
like crazy we'll have to do another
we'll have to do another video on food
for sure yeah we're gonna have to pick
your brain we'll have to bring you on
and and uh you know just talk it like
I'm going to create another like series
and just where we can come in and start
talking about a lot of these things and
we do some research definitely there
there's so much more I want to discuss
but I know people kind of you know after
a while they kind lose interest because
they're just like okay you're talking so
much it's the hustle Zone it don't
matter um but yeah there's a lot more
talk that I want to discuss later um
just covering a lot of um other things a
lot of other issues that I I
recognize within the um with the work
that I do with a lot of clients I kind
of want to address some some things for
sure and just to let everyone know that
you're all going to be okay everything
is
G to be fine if you're going through a
hard time right now write it out this
year has been traumatic for many um
there has been a lot um of loss there
has been a lot of pain suffering ups and
downs but there is a lot to look forward
to if you could just ride this out don't
give up and keep
going thank you so much Ashley for that
uh so we got a few more questions and
then we are done so the first question
is what's your favorite
snack
woo favorite snack chocolate oh I love
chocolate so much no but healthy snack
let's do the healthy SN um I absolutely
love apples with almond
butter amazing so anybody seriously go
buy some apples get some almond butter
and just put all that almond butter on
on those apples and it is just a
fantastic snack it's amazing it's really
really good do you sing in the
shower I do sing in the shower I sing
anytime I anytime I feel like singing
I'll sing I I love to sing it's just
such a dancing too I love dancing
singing anything that can really get me
into that creative mode um writing I
love to write um I love art um
everything any anything artsy I'm I'm
there 100% awesome science I love
science you love science so give me a
good book about metaphysics and Science
and all that and I'm there so um but
singing out I'll sing in the
shower what's your favorite TV show I
don't watch TV isn't that
funny was I don't watch TV I don't watch
TV I don't have I I used to watch The
Walking Dead series but that was pretty
much it I don't watch TV you know it's
so funny people say that they don't
watch TV but then they'll be like but I
watch Netflix and then I watch like this
on Netflix and that do you watch Netflix
I'll watch Netflix once in a while if
there's
something but I'm not a sit down on the
like I have too much to do in my day to
really veg on the couch you know what I
mean i' rather be focusing on um
improving my business what I can do to
expand or just write down more of my
ideas plan for the next step the whole
TV thing for me has been it's it's long
gone yeah what do what do you do on your
um your
downtime that's a good question besides
work um I I like to you know I like to
write I
like get outside much as um and catch up
with friends like catch up with the
friends and the family like I absolutely
love being around the friends and family
and then I love to just kind of veg out
and take my time take a nap you know
decompress really prep myself for the
week um but I absolutely love being
around family you know that's everything
to me I think a lot of that was because
I missed out on it so much growing up
now I value it even more because now
we're all in a better place in life and
you you know it's just life is so short
and you really want to cherish those
those um those moments and those
memories with your family MH and last
question what would you tell your little
self if you could go back in time what
would you tell that little
girl you're
worthy you're loved and
uh you're going to be
okay
just
mhm that's do wow I I really appreciate
you coming on to the hustle Zone I hope
you enjoyed it um I did I was so nervous
but the time has come the time has come
I got through it so it's all good well
that's good I I I was so excited for
this I was like I can't wait I can't
wait you know it just you know I love
the balance and um again you know you
help me even even just with what you
were saying helped me sort through you
know through thoughts um you know and
just it makes me feel I I feel like at
ease I feel comfortable I feel
comfortable with you and I think that um
you know I wish you all the success
where can where can people find
you well they can find me at well
website ww. kki elements with zed.com
services on there um just if you want to
come just to get a consult just to see
how it feels feel free to do so um but I
will be announcing something in the New
Year well before the new year um kind of
well I'm very about it um but yeah check
me out my location is on the website
send me an email um if you need any
questions answered you just want to know
a little bit about you know how to move
forward where to start shoot me an email
um but I would definitely um love to see
you if you want to come in for a
session just book an appointment with me
online so that's where you can find me
awesome and so the last thing that I
want to do uh and I usually get
everybody in the hustle Zone to
do um I do a call and response I say
welcome to the and then you say hustles
but you need to scream it
out so are you ready to do this oh God
okay okay okay okay yeah I'm ready
welcome to
the
[Laughter]
hustles we got to do that one more time
we got to do that one more time so all
right welcome to
the h hustle Zone hustle Zone yeah thank
you so much all right I really
appreciate you coming in and folks make
sure to check her out on our website um
there are some there are some questions
in the comments but these are you know
you know I would love if you guys can
reach out to Ashley personally I don't
know what her rates are or whatever but
if you have personal questions that you
want to um you know if you you need a
medium or you just need
uh just some light in certain situations
please contact her um you know even
though she's in Canada in Calgary
Alberta uh you know it doesn't mean that
she can't help I mean we're spir we're
all spiritual creatures and there's no
there's no time there's no space so
reach out to her um I want to thank
thank you again Ashley for coming out
and uh folks uh I know I've been pushing
this a lot lately because there's a lot
of people that are not getting free
websites um just because there are
people out there that are not telling
them about bti creative so it is
imperative that if you know an
entrepreneur that needs a website that's
in need like you know I'm not talking to
someone that like you know has their
stuff together but I'm talking about
someone that really needs that boost uh
we will'll definitely uh take a look at
their their their their file we'll put
them onto the the waiting list so please
check that out and uh folks again this
is just another one of those hustle Zone
shows where you know we have all
different stories like man we're talking
about you know spiritual stuff today yet
you know Ashley has the same habits as
all of the other entrepreneurs that come
on this stage and and or come on to this
this this broadcast so um thank you and
again you guys please share please like
share share share like like like go to
my Facebook or the the hustle Zone group
add yourself uh because once we launch
this magazine it's going to turn up and
make sure check check out the hustle own
t-shirts buy it um you know bit of those
proceeds are going to go back to
disabilities community and uh we haven't
sorted that out yet but we are
definitely going to do that because you
know that's what we're all about we're
about uh healing the human like you know
all us entrepreneurs are solving a need
somewhere in the world and uh thank you
guys so much